[bawling]
My chocolate, my games, Momohiki!
Where are you?
Huh?
[gasps]
Momohiki!
I missed you so much!
[smooching]
Hey, you feel kinda buff.
What happened? Hmm?
[Momohiki] Anzu, dear, I saw you
having lots of fun with that hottie.
[shrieks, screams]
I was thrown around by the plane,
and then thrown around in Times Square.
It's been rough for me.
What happened, Momohiki?
You've transformed.
You're just like a person
in those ads that say,
"Weight Training Changed My Life."
[Momohiki] I guess
you don't need me anymore.
-Goodbye to you, Anzu.
-[gasps]
Wait, Momohiki!
It's not like that.
-[meowing]
-[phone buzzing]
[moans]
Momohiki…
[meowing continues]
[buzzing continues]
[Anzu] Hm, it's the alarm.
[Anzu sighs]
Is it morning?
[meowing continues]
[exhales deeply]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
[groans]
A cat?
[shrieks]
[grunts in pain]
[Tsukasa] My tongue…
[screams]
Quiet! You and that alarm!
What… What… Wh-- What…
Just so you know,
you're the one
who made us stay up playing games,
and then you dozed off
and you wouldn't let go of my hand.
Thanks to you,
I was stuck here all night long.
I don't remember.
[Anzu] Wait a sec, was I sleeping
on his lap all night?
Ah, I'm so embarrassed!
Hold on! That's what embarrasses you?
What about walking around
in an outfit like that?
-I'm so sorry. You must have been cold.
-[sighs]
[Tsukasa] My body's hurts.
-Ugh.
-[sighs]
It's nice out now.
I gotta go home and get ready.
[Anzu] Time for serious self-reflection.
REMORSEFUL: TO BE FILLED WITH REMORSE
[approaching footsteps]
So, thanks for letting me stay here.
[Anzu] Oh, huh, no worries,
I'm sorry about everything.
-See you.
-Okay.
[door closes]
[Anzu] I meant to set my alarm
to go off way earlier than this.
I wonder if Kazuki
will have enough time to…
Oh, no, shoot!
I can't believe I forgot
to give him his lunch!
[groans]
Guess I have to give it to him at school.
-Here.
-Thanks.
-[chatter]
-[girl 1] Who does she think she is?
[girl 2] She better not think
she can get away with this!
[screams]
[groans]
[theme music]
[door closes]
#3: MY LIFE HAS BECOME A DATING SIM
[sighs]
Mm…
[Anzu] So that means
that I was holding
Kazuki's hand all night long, right?
And I even slept on his lap.
[gasps]
Wait a minute! I can't even remember
what time I dozed off.
I do remember talking to that devil and…
-and that thing was…
-[doorbell rings]
[gasps]
Who is…
What is it? Uh…
-[Anzu] Huh, Kazuki?
-Um…
So, about my place…
Aah… Are you kidding me?
Did it sink in the Tokyo Bay or something?
[comical music]
Maybe there's a weird plumbing issue
or something,
because it seems like
only my unit was flooded.
What?
[Tsukasa] My uniform
and textbooks are all drenched.
Guess I gotta skip school today.
Hey, um, can I borrow your phone?
[Anzu] Oh, huh, sure. Go ahead.
Great. Thanks.
[Anzu] I know exactly who's responsible.
They caused this ridiculous situation.
[Riri] Water blast!
Yes. Thanks a lot.
[Anzu] Gosh dang it!
-Thanks for that.
-Oh, sure.
So, everything's fine…
Never mind. I take that back.
[birds chirping]
Is there anything that I can do to help?
Yeah, why don't you give me
your phone number?
Huh? Sure.
Hmm… Just a sec.
[scribbling]
[Anzu] Here.
[Tsukasa] I'll call you
if anything comes up.
Okay.
-Oh, yeah, you forgot your lunch.
-Oh, thank you.
You packed it really well,
but, um…
-[meowing]
-…did you have to use this bag?
[Anzu] Oh, well, it seemed like
the perfect size.
And I couldn't bring you lunch.
All of your fangirls
would think of me as their enemy.
[sighs]
When I'm the one
who really made most of the lunch.
[chuckles]
Well, thank you.
Hoshino, you should get going.
-Oh, ye-- Yeah.
-I gotta go.
You've got this.
[sighs]
[Riri grunting]
[Riri laughing mischievously]
[indistinct chatter]
-Hey!
-[laughs]
[light music]
[yawns]
I'm looking for a room
to move into right away.
[Tsukasa grunts]
[old man grunts]
[Tsukasa] Huh?
Can I help you?
[old man gasps]
[old man grunts]
-[old man] Thank you very much.
-[Tsukasa] No problem.
-[school bell rings]
-[students chattering]
[Saki] Hey, Anzu.
-So, you brought your lunch today, huh?
-Yeah.
You made that all by yourself? Awesome.
[laughs awkwardly]
[Anzu] Should I confide in Saki
about the whole
complicated situation with Kazuki?
But I don't wanna drag
my precious friend into this.
BROKEN PHONE, CAN'T GET HOME,
MAJOR FLOODING
-[gasps]
-[phone buzzing]
-An unknown number's calling me?
-Oh?
-Oh, you can eat.
-Okay.
This is Anzu.
[Tsukasa] Your scrambled eggs
are too sweet.
-[gasps]
-It's a damn omelet!
Oops, sorry.
How are you calling?
-Just bought a new phone
-[Anzu] What?
Hey, are you free after school?
[Anzu] Uh, well,
I don't have anything planned.
Then, can you meet me
at Toutor by the station?
Yeah, sure.
-[Tsukasa] All right, see you later.
-[line beeps]
He hung up, jeez. Could have said more.
Your friend?
Uh, yeah… Well, let's eat then.
[Saki] Wow, looks delicious.
Sausages, sauteed spinach,
meat rolls, and scrambled eggs!
It's an omelet roll!
[Anzu] Hmm.
So I guess he did end up
having to buy a new phone after all,
even though he said he's broke.
Jeez, this is all my fault. I feel so bad.
-Wait! This is all that devil's fault!
-[Riri giggling]
-[student 1] All right, see ya!
-[student 2] See ya!
-[Rena] Oh, teacher.
-[teacher] Hm?
I heard Tsukasa's house's flooded.
Is everything all right there?
Oh, well, I was just about
to call him and find out.
Oh, but I heard that
Tsukasa's phone was broken.
What? But I think the number
he called from before
belonged to a cell phone.
No way.
I guess he must've bought one then.
All right, give me his number.
-Well, I can't help you with that.
-You're a meanie.
Well, Mister, I would still like
to hear that boy's voice.
So put the speaker on.
Hey! Come on!
CONNECTED
-[Anzu] Yes. Hello?
-What?
Um, yes, hello there.
Have I reached Kazuki's cell phone?
[Anzu] Huh? Kazuki's phone? No, uh…
-No, it's not.
-[teacher] Hm?
-Wait! What?
-Huh?
Wha--
This rent's expensive.
-Hey, don't you think that guy next to us…
-[girl] Hm-mm.
-…is way hot? Should I get his number?
-[Tsukasa] Hm?
[Tsukasa] Man, I should have worn a hat.
Huh?
Uh…
[sighs]
[Tsukasa] She's taking forever.
[gasps]
Uh…
Hey, Tsukasa.
[Tsukasa groans]
I heard all about
what happened to your place.
Oh, my gosh! It was so boring
without you at school today.
Oh, there's an open seat.
Okay, I'm gonna go get something to drink.
[sighs]
Uh, hey, sorry I took so long.
Are you, um… Are you upset?
Why did you bring them, too?
Huh? Oh, well, I…
-Ah!
-So why did Tsukasa make a call
using your phone?
Oh, well, he lives close.
And he seemed like he needed help
this morning, so I let him borrow it.
Ah, okay then. Will you tell him
to give me a call when he can?
Um, okay.
-[groans]
-[Rena grunts]
Are you going to see Tsukasa after this?
What? Um, yeah…
-My name's Rena Kashiwagi.
-And I'm Yukika Maezono.
[Rena] We're coming with you,
hope you don't mind.
[stutters]
So, that's what happened.
[sighs]
What? Hey, where are you going?
[Anzu exclaims]
-[Anzu] Huh, what are you…
-Just one today?
[Yukika] Tsukasa?
-[Rena gasps]
-[Anzu] Uh…
I only have plans to hang out with her.
[Rena] What? Wait, don't go, Tsukasa!
Huh? Um, hey…
[breathing shakily]
Hey, you sure? Isn't she your friend?
Not really. She just follows me
around all the time.
But, um, Kashiwagi, was it?
Doesn't she sort of have a thing for you?
[Tsukasa sighs]
-[Tsukasa] I'm so over it.
-[Anzu] What?
I'm nice because
she's a classmate of mine,
but I'm not interested
in dating right now.
[Anzu] Come to think of it,
he was pretty cold
to that other girl, too.
Jeez, I guess hot guys
have their own issues to deal with.
Sorry. Bringing them was wrong.
[groans softly]
No, they forced you to bring them.
Sorry, I was harsh.
That's okay. Yeah, it's hard
to set boundaries sometimes.
[light music]
-[Tsukasa] But…
-Hmm?
You're not… you're not like them, huh?
[Tsukasa] You didn't hound me
like everyone else does.
So, it feels easy.
Uh…
Well, that's good then.
[strained laugh]
[Anzu] Well, duh, I have hostages to save.
Oh, hey!
Kazuki, you said you don't want
to date anyone right now, right?
Uh, yeah.
Well, great, 'cause me too!
I mean there are
far more important things than that.
[Tsukasa] Oh, uh, okay…
[Anzu] In other words,
even if he and I become friends,
there's no chance
it will develop into a relationship.
-That dumb devil chose the wrong cutie.
-Huh?
[sinister laughter]
[Tsukasa] Uh, hello?
Oh, what'd you wanna talk about?
[Tsukasa] Right, I-- I was wondering
if I could temporarily
keep some of my stuff at your place?
[Anzu] Of course.
Did you wanna bring it over now?
I'm about to head off to work.
But I have a realtor looking for a room.
I see.
[Anzu] His parents must live far away.
Should I let him stay at my place again?
[Anzu gasps]
That devil must've flooded Kazuki's place
to make this whole thing happen!
Then they kept him at my place
and broke his phone!
It's too much drama to put on one person.
Hey, I'll, um, reimburse you
for your phone,
but I can't do it all at once.
I'm thinking about
getting a part-time job soon.
-[cell phone rings]
-[both] Huh?
Oh, good, it's the realtor.
-I'm sorry.
-[Anzu] It's cool.
Yes.
Hmm.
So, it feels easy.
[Anzu] I thought the exact same thing
about him that night he stayed over.
I will admit I kinda like that we feel
so comfortable around each other.
What'd they say?
Apparently, there aren't
any rooms available now.
What?
[Tsukasa] It seems
they all filled up recently.
[growls]
[Anzu] What if this was
that devil's handiwork, too?
Good news is there will be one
opening up, but not for another month.
-[Anzu groans]
-[sighs]
[Tsukasa] You know, the cost of the phone
is about the same price
as a month of rent.
[groans]
[Tsukasa] Hey, if it's cool with you…
Huh?
How about for a month, I stay
at your place and we call it even.
[gasps]
-What?
-[evil laughter]
Huh? Stay at my place for a month?
I'm not asking you
to let me stay there for nothing.
I'll help out with the chores, of course.
Chores?
[Tsukasa] When I don't have work,
I'll make dinner and the next day's lunch.
[Anzu] Uh, oh…
And if "that thing" comes back,
I'll get rid of it.
[narrator] Roaches are unseemly,
so instead, cake.
And as for me,
it's close to where I work,
so it'll be a huge help.
[Anzu] What should I do?
His conditions
are too delicious to pass up!
Uh, but still,
knowing that stinking devil…
-Ouch!
-Um, let me see that.
-[gasps]
-[smooching]
[Anzu] He'll just set up
insanely cheesy situations over and over.
-[screams]
-Oh, sorry!
I didn't mean to, hon.
[exclaims]
[Anzu] That must be
their entire intention!
[boy moans]
[giggles]
[grunts]
My bad, um,
it's a crazy favor to ask of you.
[Anzu] No, no, Not at all.
If you're okay with it,
I don't mind having you stay at my place.
That would be great.
[laughing awkwardly]
[Anzu] Shoot! I responded impulsively
out of this sense of guilt.
[Tsukasa] Would you explain it all
to your parents, too?
[sighs]
No worries there.
They won't have any issues with it.
[both] Sure, it's fine by me!
-[meowing]
-[phone buzzing]
[Anzu moans]
[meowing continues]
[grunts]
That dream.
Even I think it was pretty pathetic.
What a crazy dream.
Me living with a hot guy.
[bright music]
You're finally awake.
[Anzu] It wasn't a dream.
It's all coming back to me now.
Oh, wow, good morning.
Morning. You've got an early bed hair.
Yay! You're actually
making my lunch for me.
[Tsukasa] Well, that was part of the deal.
[sighs]
[Anzu] Amazing. I get to wake up
to a cutie making lunch in my kitchen.
Seriously, hot guys are hot
no matter what they do.
Kazuki, you're an early bird, huh.
You just wake up late.
Yeah.
[Anzu] Now that I think about it,
he did seem to be really tired yesterday.
-[Anzu] Long day?
-[Tsukasa] Yeah.
I'm gonna take a bath and crash.
[Anzu] First, he cleaned up
his totally flooded place,
and then he did
like a million loads of laundry,
and he had to be at work late.
And after all that, he's still up
making us lunch this morning.
-[Tsukasa] Hoshino, do you eat breakfast?
-Hm.
Yes, I do!
All right, then I'll make something quick.
[Anzu exclaims]
[Anzu] Thanks, Mom.
[Tsukasa] Yeah, yeah.
WEATHER FORECAST
[Tsukasa] Here you go.
Yay!
[chuckles]
Time to eat!
Ha, um!
[munches]
[delighted moan]
Oh, I need gym clothes.
-[Anzu] Um, they were still drying.
-I'll go get them.
-Um, can you pack my lunch for me?
-[Anzu] Yeah.
[Anzu] I don't have to make lunch
or even breakfast.
And he is a feast for the eyes.
This might be a great situation after all.
And I haven't seen
that devil around either.
Good morning!
-Ugh, speak of the devil!
-Oh, jeez.
[giggles]
Have you been enjoying
your oh-so-romantic dating-sim scenarios?
Why don't you shut up?
You put Kazuki through too much!
Be more considerate!
Yeah, yeah, you say that,
but you've been stuffing your face
with breakfast like a hamster.
-[Anzu] Shut up!
-[munching]
And just so you know,
Kazuki isn't interested
in dating anyone right now.
Too bad! You chose the wrong guy!
You're a big stupid dummy.
[humming mockingly]
-[grunts]
-You're the stupid one, Anzu!
Romance is unpredictable
because people always change their minds.
And plus, did you forget what I told you?
You're about to live
a dating sim-lifestyle
surrounded by hotties…
-Oh, watch your step!
-[giggles]
…in real life.
-[both grunt]
-[doorbell dings]
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Who's here so early?
-Ooh…
-Be right there.
-[chuckles]
[Anzu] Hm? Our school uniform? Who is it?
I'm not done, so don't disappear!
-I still have a lot to say.
-[Riri] Sure, sure!
[Anzu] Coming.
-Huh?
-[Junta] Morning.
[bright music]
How did you sleep, Anzu?
[giggles nervously]
Did you wake up late? Time for school.
[Anzu] Who is this tall drink of water?
Um… Uh…
-Have we met somewhere before?
-[Junta] What?
[Junta laughs]
Wait, what are you saying?
You still asleep?
Don't tell me you forgot your old friend.
[Anzu] My old friend?
[Tsukasa] Hoshino, what are you doing?
You should get going.
Huh?
Uh.
[Anzu gasps]
[Anzu] Dearest Mom and Dad,
how's life in the United States going?
I've been forced
to live a sad and lonely life
without my three greatest desires.
But then a super hot guy became
my roommate which feels majorly awkward.
Next, a childhood friend
who I know absolutely nothing about
suddenly appeared.
And now, everything is about
to get awfully complicated.
A fanfare, please!
And a big congratulations!
Did you fall for my little trick?
I bet now you don't feel like
skipping the ending, right?
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪